[{"question": "Choose a correct statement.\nint a = 12 + 3 * 5 / 4 - 10\n", "option1": "A) 12, 3, 5, 4 and 10 are Operators.\u00a0\n+, -, * and / are Operands.\u00a0\n= is an increment operator.", "option2": "B) 12, 3, 5, 4 and 10 are Operands.\u00a0\n+, -, * and / are Operators.\u00a0\n= is decrement operator.", "option3": "C) 12, 3, 5, 4 and 10 are Operands.\u00a0\n+, -, * and / are Operators.\u00a0\n= is an assignment operator.", "option4": "D) 12, 3, 5, 4 and 10 are Operands.\u00a0\n+, -, * and / are Logical Operators.\u00a0\n= is an assignment operator.", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "Operator % in C Language is called.?", "option1": "A) Percentage Operator", "option2": "B) Quotient Operator", "option3": "C) Modulus", "option4": "D) Division", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "Output of an arithmetic expression with integers and real numbers is ___ by default.?", "option1": "A) Integer", "option2": "B) Real number", "option3": "C) Depends on the numbers used in the expression.", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "Choose a right statement.\nint a = 10 + 4.867;\n", "option1": "A) a = 10", "option2": "B) a = 14.867", "option3": "C) a = 14", "option4": "D) compiler error.", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "Choose a right statement.\nint a = 3.5 + 4.5;\n", "option1": "A) a = 0", "option2": "B) a = 7", "option3": "C) a = 8", "option4": "D) a = 8.0", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "Choose a right statement.\nfloat var = 3.5 + 4.5;\n", "option1": "A) var = 8.0", "option2": "B) var = 8", "option3": "C) var = 7", "option4": "D) var = 0.0", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "Choose right statement.\nint main()\n{\n    float c = 3.5 + 4.5;\n    printf(\"%f\", c);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 8.0", "option2": "B) 8.000000", "option3": "C) 8", "option4": "D) 7", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "Choose a right statement.\nint main()\n{\n    float c = 3.5 + 4.5;\n    printf(\"%d\", (int)c);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 8.0", "option2": "B) 8.000000", "option3": "C) 7", "option4": "D) 8", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Choose a right statement.\nint a = 5/2;\nint b = 5.0/2;\nint c = 5 / 2.0;\nint d = 5.0/2.0;\n", "option1": "A) a = 2, b = 2, c = 2, d= 2", "option2": "B) a = 2, b = 2.0, c = 2, d= 2.0", "option3": "C) a = 2, b = 2.5, c = 2.5, d= 2.5", "option4": "D) a = 2.5, b = 2.5, c = 2.5, d= 2.5", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " Choose a right statement.\nfloat a = 5/2;\nfloat b = 5/2.0;\nfloat c = 5.0/2;\nfloat d = 5.0/2.0;\n", "option1": "A) a=2.5, b=2.5, c=2.5, d=2.5", "option2": "B) a=2, b=2.5, c=2.5, d=2.5", "option3": "C) a=2.0, b=2.5, c=2.5, d=2.5", "option4": "D) a=2.0, b=2.0, c=2.0, d=2.0", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " If both numerator and denominator of a division operation in C language are integers, then we get.?", "option1": "A) Expected algebraic real value", "option2": "B) Unexpected integer value", "option3": "C) Compiler error.", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " Choose a right statement.\nint var = 3.5;\n", "option1": "A) a = 3.5", "option2": "B) a = 3", "option3": "C) a = 0", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " Choose a right statement.\nint main()\n{\n    int var = 3.5;;\n    printf(\"%f\", var);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 3.500000", "option2": "B) 3", "option3": "C) 3.5", "option4": "D) 0.000000", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of the program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a = 25%10;\n    printf(\"%d\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 2.5", "option2": "B) 2", "option3": "C) 5", "option4": "D) Compiler error.", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " Can you use C Modulo Division operator % with float\u00a0and int?", "option1": "A) Only int variables = Okay", "option2": "B) Only float variables = Okay", "option3": "C) int or float combination = Okay", "option4": "D) Numerator int variable, Denominator any variable = Okay", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " What is the output of the C program with Modulo Division operator with - or Negative numbers.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a = -25%-10;\n    int b = -25%10;\n    int c = 25%-10;\n    \n    printf(\"%d %d %d\", a, b, c);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 5 -5\u00a0 -5", "option2": "B) 5 -5 5", "option3": "C) -5 -5 5", "option4": "D) 5 5 5", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of the program.?\nint main()\n{\n    float a = 45;\n    printf(\"%f\", a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 45", "option2": "B) 45.0", "option3": "C) 45.000000", "option4": "D) 0.000000", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the priority of operators *, / and % in C language.?", "option1": "A) * > / > %", "option2": "B) % > * > /", "option3": "C) Both % = / ,\u00a0\u00a0*\u00a0 are same", "option4": "D) All three operators *, / and % are same.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " In C language, which Operator group has more priority between (*, / and %) and (+, -) groups.?", "option1": "A) Both groups share equal priority.", "option2": "B) (+, -) > (*, / and %)", "option3": "C) (+, -) < (*, / and %)", "option4": "D) None of the above.", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " Associativity of C Operators *, /, %, +, - and = is.?", "option1": "A) Operators *, / and % have Left to Right Associativity. Operators + and - have Left to Right Associativity. Operator = has Right to Left Associativitiy.", "option2": "B) Operators *, / and % have Right to Left Associativity. Operators + and - have Left to Right Associativity. Operator = has Right to Left Associativitiy.", "option3": "C) Operators *, / and % have Right to Left Associativity. Operators + and - have Right to Left Associativity. Operator = has Right to Left Associativitiy.", "option4": "D) Operators *, / and % have Right to Left Associativity. Operators + and - have Right to Left Associativity. Operator = has Left to Right Associativitiy.", "ans": "A"}]
